<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="http://www.heigl.org/docbook/xsl/html/chunk.xsl" ?>
<!DOCTYPE book PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.2//EN" "http://www.heigl.org/docbook/dtd/docbookx.dtd"[
<!ENTITY cost SYSTEM "cost.xml">
<!ENTITY technical SYSTEM "technical.xml">
]>
<book id="phpug" lang="en">
    <bookinfo>
        <title>PHP.ug - An international meeting point for the PHP-community</title>
        <author><firstname>Andreas</firstname><surname>Heigl</surname></author>
        <copyright><year>2012</year><holder>Andreas Heigl</holder></copyright>
    </bookinfo>
    <chapter id="phpug.introduction">
    <title>Purpose</title>
    <para>
        This Website provides a location for PHP usergroups worldwide to 
        advertise their existence, their meetings and their contact-details.
    </para>
    <para>
        For that we include a map on the frontpage that displays every 
        registered location worldwide. The User can then select the nearest UG 
        and see the relevant informations like next meeting and 
        contact-informations
    </para>
    <para>
        From their you can jump to their website immediately
    </para>
    <para>
        Also a shortlink is provided for every UG so their website can be 
        reached using an UTL like http://php.ug/ffm for the Usergroup at 
        Frankfurt/Main in Germany or http://php.ug/benelux for the UG in the 
        Benelux-Countries.
    </para>
    <para>
        For that every Usergroup can register by providing a unique identifier 
        (ffm or benelux), a website and some contact-informations (mainly email, 
        but twitter, facebook or Chat are also possible) and a location where 
        (or around where) the meetings are held.
    </para>
    <para>
        The provided email-address will then get the login information to change
        and maintain the provided data.
    </para>
    <para>
        All Usergroups will have to verify their existence at least once a year 
        so we can archive inactive groups.
    </para>
    <para>
        The meeting schedule will be retrieved weekly from an iCalendar-File the 
        usergroup should provide on their Website. That makes it easier to 
        maintain a consistent Dataset of the schedules as the UG only needs to
        maintain their local calendar and this website will retrieve that 
        information. If no URL to that calendar is given, then no 
        meeting-schedule will be displayed.
    </para>
    <para>
        NO statistics will be provided. 
    </para>
</chapter>
    &cost;
    &technical;
</book>